Akshay Tiwari

Web Developer

I'm a multi-disciplinary Web-App Developer who's delivered creative and engaging tech solutions to various organizations. I have almost two years of hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, and JavaScript as well as JavaScript frameworks like React. Building state-of-the-art, easy to use, user-friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine.

me@akshaydev.tech X

7011965610

delhi. India

akshaydev.tech

linkedin.com/in/akshaytiwari12 in

github.com/tvibhu12 🦪

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer intern

Sensus Labs

01/2019 - 07/2019 San Francisco(US) | Remote Sensor powered machine learning platform for retail analytics

- Design Front-End And Back-End for ML based API.
- Use ReactJs and NodeJs for Front-End and Back-End.
- Add login and register feature using PostgresSQL.
- Working in a Team which has different skills set.
- Developing Responsive & High performance UI/UX with rich frontend interactions and experience.

Front-end developer

VOZ Tech Pvt. Ltd

07/2019 - 12/2019

IIT Kharagpur (IN) | Remote

Achievements/Tasks

- Developing Responsive & High-performance UI/UX with rich frontend interactions and experience.
- Cross Browser & Platform supported UI that follows modern best practices.
- Refactored the code and developed some components.

React developer

W3Dev

01/2020 - 08/2020

delhi

a product development agency, helping your ideas to get converted into Reality.

Achievements/Tasks

- Working on different types of projects.
- Working with new frameworks like SVELTE, IONIC with REACT.
- Developed a payment gateway with web SDK for clients.

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Linky - A link shortner

- It's free, no login required.
- Used NextJs for server-side rendering which makes it fast in comparison to Client-side rendering.
- Use Node js for backend and MongoDB for Database.
- Backend deployed on Heroku and front-end on Vercel.

Form builder unding drag and drop (06/2020 - 06/2020) ♂

 I used purely react to develop this app. Users can drag and drop the element to create their own form and can export JSON data for the LIQUID file or react app.

Memory Game (08/2018 - 08/2018) &

 This is a memory game you make a match in this game. How much can you fast? You should try this game is really cool and interesting game. I used HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Smart Brains (12/2018 - 12/2018) 🗗

 This is a web project for face recognition (only one face can be recognition). The front end is made by React, the back end uses the Express.js and database is Postgresql. This whole project deployed on the Heroku.

Random Quote machine (03/2018 - 03/2018) 🗹

 I used public API on this website. Users click on the "New Quote" button it will give you a new quote every time and you can share them on your Twitter account. i used HTML,CSSS, BootStrap.public API

EDUCATION

B.Tech in Computer Science

MSIT

3 year Diploma in Computer Science GTBPI

High School

Pt. YadRam Sec. public school

ACHIEVEMENTS

Google Reskill development program (02/2018 - 11/2018)